A Finding Aid to the American Federation of Arts Records, 1895-1993 (bulk 1909-1969), in the Archives of American Art AAA.amerfeda
Archives of American Art
Scadron, Christopher: 58-16
Scalamandre, Wallpapers, Inc: NY-14
Scalini, Guiditta: 57-34
Scanavino, Emilio: 60-20, 61-4
Scelzio, Domenico: 58-9
Schadel, Hans: 58-28
Schadelin, Eva: 61-1
Schaeffer, H. Bella: 56-2
Schaffer, Rose: 58-3
Schaffner, Alexander: 61-1
Schallinger, Max: 56-2
Schamberg, Morton L.: 55-15
Schamout, Jamil: 56-29
Schanker, Louis: 53-2, 55-3, 56-2, 56-26, 58-43, 60-24, ME-7, NY-3
Scharf, William: 56-9, 58-12
Schatz, B.: 58-36
Schatz, L.: 58-36
Schatz, Z.: 58-36
Schauffelein, Hans Leonard: 57-37, 64-9
Schauss, W.: ME-29
Schecter, Pearl: 58-16
Scheibe, Richard: NE-48
Scheibler, Franz: 53-21
Scheid, Karl: 61-1
Scheier, Edwin & Mary: 57-6
Scheler, Max G.: 57-16
Scheper-Berkenkamp, Lou: NE-48
Scherschel, Frank: 58-A&B, L-3
Scherschel Joe: 58-A&B
Schettino, Aniello G.: ME-75
Scheving, Gunnlaugur: 66-2
Schiavone, Andrea: 64-6
Schickel, William: 53-25, 58-16
Schiefer Johannes: 52-7
Schieferdecker, Ivan: 65-11
Schifrin, Arnold: 55-5
Schillig, Erna: 61-1
Schimpff, Mary: 54-43
Schinkel: 63-19
Schiwetz, E.M. (Buck): 57-23
Schlanger, Ben: 62-14, 64-35
Schlemmer, Oskar: 56-7
Schliff, John D.: 58-20
Schmahl, Matilda E.: 59-6
Schmaltz, Roy E.: 53-24
Schmegner, Theobald: 58-15
Schmid, Elsa: 58-16
Schmidt, Arnold: ME-75
Schmidt, Charles W.: 65-11
Schmidt, Christian F.: 57-14, 60-5
Schmidt, Julius: 58-12, 63-31, 64-20
Schmidt, W. Fritz: 59-27
Schmidt, Willi: 53-15
Schmidt-Rottluff, Karl: 54-16, 56-7, 59-36, ME-32
Schnakenberg, Henry E.: 53-5, 62-30, 64-3
Schneider, Gerard: 56-21
Schneider, JoAnne: 64-29, 64-30
Schneider-Esleben, Paul: 58-28
Schnell, Shirley: 65-7
Schnieder, George (Father): ME-75
Schnur, Martin: 62-15
Schober, Sally: 58-32
Schon, Erhard: 64-9
Schongauer, Martin: 55-10, 57-37, 62-18, 63-17, 64-9, NY-9
School of Ceramics, Madrid: 61-1
Schooley, Elmer: 53-16, 56-26
Schor, Ilya: 58-16
Schor, Johann Paul: 59-40
Schott, Hyden: 56-27
Schrag, Karl: 53-5, 55-20, 56-25, 56-26, 57-32, 57-36, 58-3, 59-49, 60-3, 60-24, 61-1, 61-15, 62-3, 62-8, 62-30, 63-12, 64-7, 64-31, ME-7, ME-26, NY-3
Schreckengost, Viktor: 53-5
Schreiber, Georges: 56-1
Schroeder, Lynn: 58-6, 60-3
Schueler, Jon: 58-5, 58-12, 60-1, 60-9
Schuldtz Alexander: 57-40
Schuler, Robert T.: 64-7
Schulteiss, Carl: 53-5
Schulthess, Emil: 59-56, 62-45
Schultz, Anabel: 60-5
Schultze, Bernard: 54-18
Schulz, Rudolf: 53-15
Schumacher, Emil: 59-36
Schussele, Christian: 59-6
Schutz-Wolff, Johannes: 59-36
Schutzer, Paul: 58-A&B
Schutzman, Leo: 57-ee
Schwaar, Walter: 53-21
Schwabacher, Ethel: 59-23, ME-59
Schwachman, Irene: 62-45
Schwarcz, June: 57-6, 60-12
Schwartz, Aubrey: 58-40, 60-3, 63-12
Schwartz Daniel: 56-13
Schwartz, Harold: 61-30
Schwartz, Knut: 57-40
Schwartz, Lester: 51-1
Schwartz, Manfred: 55-3, 57-10, 58-5
Schwartz, Rochelle K.: 62-10
Schwartz, S.: 58-36
Schwarz, Hanna: 53-24
Schwarz, Joseph: 59-1, 61-35
Schwarz, Rudolf: 58-28
Schwarz & Bernard, Rudolf & Josef: 58-28
Schweig, G.: 58-36
Schweikher, Paul: 62-14, 64-35
Schweikher & Elting: 58-1
Schweitzer, Gertrude: 53-8
Schwerin, Ludwig: 58-15
Schwitters, Kurt: 59-14, 62-18, 64-10
Scialoja, Toti: 58-23, 60-15
Scordia, Antonio: 58-23, 59-35
Scornavacca, Tony: 61-35
Scott, David: 53-5
Scott, George Gilbert (Sir): 61-22
Scott, Isabel: 57-6
Scott, John: 64-23
Scott, Ken: 62-15
Scott, Louise: 64-30
Scott, William: 62-15
Scuris, Stephanie: 58-39
Se-duk, Yi: 58-33
Seabrook, G.M.: 56-18
Sebring, Burr: 58-32, 64-23
Secrest, James D.: 57-6
Secrest, Russell: 62-10
Sedlacek, Vojtch: 56-15
Segal, George: 60-43
Segal, Simon: 59-5
Segal, Yonny: 54-14
Seibel, Fred O.: 57-3
Seibert, Edward J.: 64-21
Seide, Charles: 56-2
Seidl, Alfred: 61-1
Seidler, Doris: 58-3, 60-3, 62-3, 64-7
Seitz, William: 60-5
Sekimachi, Kay: 60-12, 62-15, 64-23
Sekino, Junichiro: 56-21
Selan-Gliha, Vilko: 56-21
Selbing, John: 56-3
Seley, Jason: 63-29, 65-11
Seliger: NY-20
Seliger, Charles: 55-21, 58-5, 58-43
Seligmann, Kurt: 55-21, 56-1, 57-10, 57-32, 57-36, 58-5, 59-1, 59-19, 60-4, 61-15, 61-26, 62-1
Selim Jewad: 56-29
Selim, Lorna: 56-29
Sella, Alvin: 61-35
Seltzer, Deppie: 53-16
Seltzer, Phyllis: 62-3
Semser, Charles: 58-39
Semuth: 54-25
Senn, Otto H.: 53-21
Sennhauser, John: 58-26
Senska, Frances: 56-26
Senungetuk, Ronald: 62-10
Seoane, Luis: 60-17
Sepeshy, Zoltan L.: 55-2, 55-19, ME-73
Sera, Johan K.: 62-10
Serisawa, Sueo: 56-19, 58-42, 61-7
Serlio: 63-19
Sernesi, Raffaello: 63-10
Serpan, Iroslav: 57-27
Sert, Jackson & Gourley: 63-16
Servandoni, Giovanni Niccolo: 59-40, 63-19
Sesshu: ME-40
Sessler, Alfred: 55-20
Seuphor, Michel: 61-4
Seurat, Georges: 57-18, ME-32
Severini, Gino: 57-34, 58-23, 64-10
Severn Arthur: 62-12
Sewall, Harriot: 64-1
Sewell, Helen: VA-53-1
Seymour, David: 59-56
Shadbolt, Jack Leonard: 54-27, 59-3
Shaeffer Norbert: 55-22
Shaffer, Gary: 62-3
Shaffer, Verne: 57-31
Shahn, Ben: 53-1, 54-10, 55-13, 56-24, 57-2, 57-9, 58-16, 59-6, 59-7, 59-24, 59-31, 60-22, 60-27, 62-28, 62-31, 64-28, 65-1, ME-7, ME-23, ME-41, ME-73, NY-5
Shaier, Mary: 64-30
Shakespeare: 58-36
Shaltiel, B.: 58-36
Shaner, G. David: 60-5
Shapiro, David: 55-5, 56-13
Shapiro, Hilda: 63-7
Shapiro, Seymour: 60-43
Shapleigh, Frank H.: 64-3
Sharaku, Toshusai: 58-17
Sharpiro, Miriam: 64-12
Sharrer, Honore: 55-13
Shaub, Paul: 56-25, 58-3
Shaw, Charles: 55-3
Shaw, Kendall: NY-17
Shaw, Richard Norman: 61-22
Sheeler, Charles: 54-25, 55-9, 55-13, 55-15, 57-15, 58-34, 59-6, 59-24, 59-31, 60-13, 60-27, 64-4, 64-28, 65-2, ME-7, ME-23, ME-31, NY-11, NY-20
Sheets, Millard: 62-31
Shep, Larry: 58-32
Shephard, Rupert: 56-21
Shepherd, Don: ME-75
Shepley, Bulfinch, Richardson & Abbott: 63-16
Sherlock, William P.: 64-5
Sherman, Phyllis: 56-26
Sherman, Sarai: NY-10
Sherry, William Grant: 56-27
Shertze,r Gerald: 59-6
Sherwood, Nancy: 60-5
Sherwood, Mills & Smith: 63-16, 64-11
Shew William: 54-12
Shibuya, Kazuko: 65-12
Shifrin, Roy: ME-75
Shima, Ichiro: 65-12
Shindler, Antonio Zeno: 64-1
Shinn, Everett: 60-24, 62-17, 64-3, NY-19
Shinoda, Toko: 64-10
Shirlaw, Walter: 61-3, 64-3
Shirley, Gerald: 58-6
Shobaken, Bruce: 55-14
Shober, Charles: ME-29
Shohannah: 56-12
Short, Sam B.: 62-34
Sharde: 51-15
Shrode, Marejon Sue: 51-15
Shuff-Shir, Lily: 56-25
Shugg, R.: 57-17
Shukri, Akram: 56-29
Shunsho, Katsukawa: 58-17, 60-38
Shute, Ben: 61-35
Shute, Nell C.: 56-13
Siegal, Arthur: 51-9, 57-25
Siegel, Ellen: 61-17, 62-15, 64-23
Siegel, Paul: 57-17
Siegriest, Lundy: 55-5, 57-12, 58-7, ME-33, ME-42
Sievan, Maurice: 55-3, 64-30
Signac, Paul: 58-34, 60-14, 62-5
Signorini, Telemaco: 63-10
Sigurdsson, Steinthor: 66-2
Sikeliotis, George: 56-29
Silk, George: 58-A&B, 59-56
Silva, Amandio: 56-15
Silverman, Burton: 56-13
Silverman, Mel: 60-3
Silverstein, Louis: 60-37
Silz, Arthur: 56-2
Simberg-Ehrstrom, Beata: 62-15
Simches, Frances E.: 60-5
Simkhovitch, Helena: 53-20
Simpson, Lusby: 59-25
Simpson, Maxwell Stuart: 56-2
Simpson, Thomas: 65-6
Simpson-Middleman: 55-2
Simunovic, Frano: 59-16
Singer, Arnold: 58-3
Singer, Gail: 62-8
Singier, Gustave: 54-18, 58-15, 60-14
Sinsabaugh, Art: 57-25
Sintenis, Renee: NE-48
Sinton Nell: 58-7
Siporin, Mitchell: 56-27, 57-28, 58-5
Sirani, Giovanni Andrea: 64-6
Sironi: 51-18
Sironi, Mario: 57-34, 58-23
Siskind, Aarpon: 57-25
Sisson, Lawrence: 53-12, 57-31
Sitllman, Ary: 55-3
Sitter, Inger: 57-40, 58-15
Sitton, James: 65-11
Sivard, Robert: 55-19, 65-2
Sizemore, Mary: 53-26
Skidmore, Owings & Merrill: 59-15, 61-31, 63-16, 65-3, 65-9
Skinner, A.: NY-13
Skiold, Bergit: 60-15
Skovgaard, Joakim: 54-16
Skowronski, Hella: 62-15
Skrede, Agnar: 57-14
Skulason, Thorvaldur: 66-2
Slater, Eva: 55-6
Sloan, John: 54-25, 55-16, 57-2, 59-24, 60-13, 60-24, 60-27, 62-28, 62-30, 65-2, ME-31, ME-41, NY-9, NY-19
Sloane, Mary: 56-27
Slobodkin, Louis: VA-53-1
Slobodkina, Esphyr: 55-3, 59-1
Slottag, Jack: 53-26
Slowan, John: ME-7
Slutzky, Robert: 60-41
Slwan, John: 59-6
Small, Dorothy May: 60-5
Smarkusz, Vincent T.: 53-26
Smillie, George Henry: 60-28
Smillie, James D.: 64-3
Smith: ME-49
Smith, Aruthur: 57-6
Smith, Charles William: ME-7
Smith, David: 53-5, 55-12, 56-22, 59-31, 60-14, 61-25, 61-29, 63-31, 65-1
Smith, Donald E.: 57-10
Smith, Edith M.: 56-2
Smith, Eirikur: 66-2
Smith, Francis Hopkinson: 64-3
Smith, G.E. Kidder: 64-11
Smith, Hamilton: 63-16, 65-3
Smith, Hassel: 65-11
Smith, J. Warwick: 62-12
Smith, John Rubens: 64-1
Smith, Leon Polk: 60-41, 63-30, 64-2, 64-26, 65-4
Smith, Loran: 65-5
Smith, Moishe: 55-20, 58-3
Smith, Oliver: 59-19
Smith, Paul: 54-8, 57-6, 58-32
Smith, R.A.: 62-3, 64-7
Smith, Roger: 64-28
Smith, Thomas R.: 62-10
Smith, Vernan: 64-30
Smith, W. Eugene: 59-56
Smith, William A.: 53-5, 53-8, 56-25
Smithson Robert: 61-22
Smyly, Susan: 62-10
Snellman-Hanninen, Airi: 57-14
Snider, Robert S.: 62-10
Snipper, Martin: 55-5
Snow, Doug: 53-24
Snyder, Jerome: 55-13, 56-24
Snyder, Lewis E.: 62-10
Soane, John (Sir): 61-22
Sobotka, Ruth: 59-19
Sochurek, Howard: 58-A&B, 59-56
Soderberg, Wesley: 64-7
Soglow, O.: ME-28
Soglu, Muella: 56-29
Sokol, Bill: 56-25
Sokole, Miron: 53-5
Soldati, Atanasio: 58-23
Soldenhoff, Alex: 54-16
Soldner, Paul A.: 55-22
Soldner, Paul E.: 57-6
Solimena, Francesco: 62-36
Solman, Joseph: 55-2, 55-3
Soloducha, A.V.: 53-24
Solomon, Hyde: 60-43, 63-1, ME-73
Solomon, Syd: 53-5, 55-5, 56-2, 56-13, 57-35, 61-35
Solow, Seymour: 57-16
Somaini, Francesco: 60-20
Sommer, Madelon: 53-26
Sonderborg, K.H.R.: 61-4
Sonenberg, Jack: 55-20, 56-25, 58-3, 60-3
Sorenson Richard: 53-26
Soudeikine: 63-19
Soulages, Pierre: 57-9, 57-27, 58-15, 60-14
Soulange, Tessier: ME-29
Souply, Emile: 61-1
Southworth & Hawes: 56-5
Souza: 59-13
Sowers, Robert: 58-16
Soyer, Moses: 53-5, 56-2, 64-3, ME-73
Soyer Raphael: 56-2, 57-11, 58-40, 62-28, 62-30, 63-33, 64-3, 64-31, 65-2, ME-73, NY-18
Spacal, Luigi: 54-16, 56-21
Space Design Group, Inc.: 61-30
Spaventa, George: 60-42
Spazzapan, Luigi: 58-23, 59-35
Speckaert, Hans: 62-20
Speicher, Eugene: 57-11, 62-31
Speight Francis: 63-3
Spencer, Niles: 55-11, 55-16, 60-27, 64-30
Spencer & Ambrose Eldridge T. & William Clement: SD-8
Sperry, Robert: 57-14
Sperschneider, Ragna: 61-1
Speyer, Friederich: 64-1
Speyer, Nora: 56-2
Spille, Dean: 53-26
Spinchorn, Carl: 64-29
Spivak, Max: 53-25
Sponsler, Edwin: 53-5
Sprague, Arthur H.: 60-5
Spranger: 54-11
Sprinchorn, Carl: 64-30, 64-31
Springett, Sabino: 60-17
Springinklee, Hans: 55-10, 62-18
Spruance, Benton: 53-1, 54-16, 54-18, 56-15, 58-3, ME-7, NE-96
Spruce, Everett: 57-23, 59-50, 60-1
Spyropoulos, Jannis: 61-11
Squier, Jack: 57-12, 57-31, 60-42, 62-40, ME-56, NY-10
Staack, Zora: 56-21
Stackpole, Peter: 58-A&B
Stage, John L.: 57-16
Stahly, Francois: 61-2
Staikov, Veselin: 56-21
Stakiewicz, Richard: 62-41
Stallings, Hal: 57-14
Stamos, Theodoros: 54-10, 55-8, 56-2, 58-42, 58-43, 60-22, 60-27, 61-23, 64-19, ME-41, ME-49, ME-59, ME-65, ME-73
Stanford, James R.: 62-45
Stanger, Barbara Wechsler: 57-14
Stankiewicz, Richard: 56-12, 59-14, 60-4, 60-9, 62-27, 64-20, NY-10
Stanley, John Mix: 59-34, 61-3
Stanley Mack: 52-11
Stasack, Edward: ME-73
Staschen, Sirley: 62-18
Stashin, Leo: 59-56
Stasik, Andrew: 60-15, 64-7
Stasock, Edward: 56-25
Stavert, Nancy E.: 53-24
Stea, Cesare: 52-4, 56-2
Stearns, Junius Brutus: 58-27
Stearns, Pamela: 62-10
Stebbins, N.L.: 64-28
Steczynski, John M.: 60-3
Steele, Gordon: 55-2
Stefanelli, Joseph: 56-2, 59-1, 61-15
Stefansson, Jon: 66-2
Steg, James Louis: 56-25, 56-26, 58-3, 62-3, 64-7, NY-3
Steichen, Edward: 56-5, 58-20, 62-25, 64-28, NY-1
Steig, William: 55-13, ME-28
Steiger, Rudolf: 53-21
Stein, Joseph Allen: SD-8
Stein, Walter: 53-14, 58-40
Steinberg, Saul: 55-13, 57-3, 59-6, ME-59, VA-55-1
Steinbock, Heimos & Hannes: 61-1
Steiner, Albert H.: 53-21
Steiner, Ralph: 56-5
Steiner, Sylvia: 61-1
Steinhardt, Jacob: 54-16, 58-36
Steinlen, Theophile: 62-5
Steinmetz, William O.: 53-24
Stella: 54-25
Stella, Frank: 61-23, 64-26
Stella, Joseph: 55-15, 60-13, 62-30, 63-1, ME-31
Steltzner, Richard M.: 62-10
Stemos, Theodoros: NY-10
Stenstadvold, Haakon: 57-40
Stephens, Jr., Curtis: 64-23
Stephens, Jr., Edward John: ME-55
Steriadi, Jean Al: 56-21
Sterling, James: 56-2
Sternberg, Charlotte J.: 52-11
Sternberg, Harry: 58-3, 62-45, ME-7
Sterne: ME-49
Sterne, Hedda: 55-9, 55-13, 60-22, 61-29, 62-37, 63-7, ME-59
Sterne, Maurice: 57-11, 57-30, 59-6, 64-29, 64-30, ME-41
Sterner, Harold: 57-1
Sternglass, Lisa Jane: 57-12
Sterrett, Cliff: 57-3
Stettinius, Samuel Enredy: 64-1
Steuart, George: 61-22
Steuecheli, Werner: 53-21
Steumpfig, Walter: 53-12
Stevens, Alfred: 61-22
Stevens, Bernice A.: 60-5
Stevens, Edward John: 55-21, ME-26
Stevens, John R.: 57-6
Stevens, Margo: 58-39
Stevens, Preston S.: 59-12
Stevens, Virginia Hill: 61-35
Stevens, Walter H.: 57-12
Stevenson, Beulah: 55-3, 58-3
Stevenson, Hugh: 59-19
Steward, Donn: 53-16, 56-26, NY-3
Stewart, Donald J.: 64-21
Stewart, Marion: 57-6
Stich, Otto: 53-15
Stieglitz, Alfred: 56-5, 62-25, 64-5, 64-28, NY-1
Still, Clifford: ME-59
Stillwell, E. Burton: NE-96
Stimmer, Tobias: 64-9
Stine, Richard: 62-31
Stock, Joseph: 58-14, 62-2
Stockmarr, Erik: 52-5
Stocksdale, Bob: 55-22, 57-6, ME-75
Stohrer, Walter: 64-14
Stoltenberg, Sibley Smith Dondad: 56-27
Stolz, John E.: 62-10
Stolzl, Gunda Stadler: 61-1
Stone, Edward Durell: 59-15, 62-14, 63-16, 64-35, 65-3, 65-9
Stone, Helen: VA-53-1
Stor, Lorenz: 64-9
Stork, Abraham: 62-20
Stout, Myron: 60-12, 60-41
Stout Pola: 62-15
Stouter, D.G.: 62-2
Stradanus, Johannes: 63-9
Stradone, Giovanni: 58-23
Strahan, Thomas: NY-14
Strand, Paul: 56-5, 62-25, NY-1
Strater, Henry: 64-31
Strawn, Dean: 51-15
Strawn, Harold Dean: 51-15
Strebelle, Olivier: 61-1
Strecker, Thomas: 58-16
Strecker, Z. Thomas: 59-12
Strecker, Zelda: 58-25, 64-23
Streisinger, Lotte: 57-14
Strengell, Marianne: 52-7, 58-25, 62-15, 64-23
Strenger, Friedhelm: 53-15
Stretti-Zamponi,Jaromir: 56-21
Strickdale, Bob: 51-15
Strickland, John: 58-39
Strijbosch, Wim: 61-20
Strock, George: 59-56
Strologo, Serio Dello: 57-6
Strombotne, James: 60-1, 64-25, ME-75, NY-10
Stuart, Gilbert: 54-25, 60-13, 63-3, ME-7, ME-11, ME-31
Stuck, Jack: 65-11
Stucki, Jakob: 61-1
Stueland, Kari Bing & Magne: 57-40
Stuempfig, Walter: 55-9, 57-2, ME-41
Stuempfig, Jr., Walter: 63-3
Stupica, Grabriel: 59-16
Sturm, Dorothy: ME-26
Sublett, Carl: 65-11
Suemura, Shobun: 65-12
Sugai, Kumi: 58-15, 58-29, 58-42, 61-4, 63-23
Sugarman, George: 60-2, 62-40, ME-56
Sughi, Alberto: 58-40
Sugimata, Tadashi: 58-42
Sugimoto, Albert: 59-10
Sulfsted, Rosemary: 53-26
Sullivan, Louis: 59-6
Sully, Thomas: 62-17, 63-3, 64-1, MMM-4
Sumiyama: 63-21
Summer, Eugenia: 61-35
Summers, Carol: 56-25, 56-26, 58-3, 60-2, 60-3, 60-15, 62-3, 64-7, NY-3
Sundell, Britt-Louise: 57-14
Suornos, John: 56-29
Susini, Antonio: 63-9
Sussman, Richard: 58-6, 61-15, 61-25
Sustermans Justus: MMA-54-2
Sustris, Friedrich: 63-9, 64-9
Sutfin Edward (Father): 58-16
Sutherland ,Graham: 54-27, 61-4, 62-12, NE-96
Sutherland, T.: ME-29
Suydam,David L.: 62-10
Suzuki, James: 57-10, 58-42, 59-1, 59-10, 60-14, 61-7, 63-21
Suzuki, Seisei: 65-12
Svabinsky, Max: 56-21
Sveinsdottir, Juliana: 66-2
Svensson, Inez: 57-14
Swabian School: 56-16
Swan, Barbara: 55-5
Swanson, Pipsan Saarinen: 57-6
Swarz, Saul: 58-16, 62-40, ME-56
Swearingen, John: 53-26
Swift, Dick: 60-3
Swinnerton, James: 57-3
Swinton, George: 54-27
Sykes, Maltby: 53-5, 54-18
Szabo Bela Gy: 56-21
Szenes, Arpad: 62-8, 64-10
Szilard, Claire: 53-2
Szymak, John: 57-6, 60-5
Szymanski, Rolf: 64-14
T'cheng, Tsou-lin: 58-42
Taber, Isiah West: NY-1
Tabler, William B.: 61-31
Tabuchi, Yasse: 58-42
Tacca: 63-19
Tack, Augustus Vincent: 63-15
Tackett, LaGardo: 55-22
Tait, A.F.: 55-19
Tajiri, Shinkichi: 65-7
Taka, Peter: 56-1
Takaezu, Toshiko: 53-24
Takahashi, Henry: 55-22
Takahashi, Setsuro: 65-12
Takahashi, Shizue: 65-12
Takai, Teiji: 60-1
Takal, Peter: 55-20, 56-2, 56-25, 57-1, 58-3, 61-15, 61-25, 62-3
Takegoshi, Yoshiyuki: 65-12
Takehita, Natsuko: 57-12
Takemoto, Henry: 58-32, 59-12
Takis, Istrou: 56-29
Talbot, William Henry Fox: 53-20, 62-25, NY-1
Talburt, Harold: 57-3
Talleur, John: 53-5, 58-16, 58-35, 60-3, 61-22
Tam, Reuben: 55-3, 64-31, ME-73
Tamayo, Rufino: 57-9, 59-31, 60-14, 63-33, ME-32, NE-96, NY-18
Tanabe, Chikuunsai: 65-12
Tanaka: 63-21
Tanaka, Kosai: 65-12
Tanaka, Tokutaro: 62-45
Tanguy, Yves: 51-4, 61-9, 62-8
Tapies, Antonio: 57-27, 64-17
Tarbell, Edmund Charles: 57-11, 62-7, 63-1
Tarr, Louis E.: 60-5
Tassi, A.: 55-24
Tavenkin, M.: 58-36
Tavernier, Jules: 61-3
Tawney, Lenore: 57-6, 58-25, 59-12
Taylor, C.J.: 57-3
Taylor, David: 62-3
Taylor Julius: 61-17
Taylor, Najah: NY-13
Taylor, R.: ME-28
Taylor, Ralph: 60-3
Taylor, Spaulding: 64-23
Taylor, Vincent: 53-26
Tazaki, Shoichiro: 65-12
Tchelitchew, Pavel: 55-21, 57-9, 57-30, 59-6, 62-28, 63-19, ME-55
Teague, Norwood: 57-6
Teichman, Sabina: 64-30
Teis, Dan: 58-3, 61-35
Teitelbaum, Edith: 53-24
Tejima: 63-21
Tempesta, Antonio: 64-6
Temple, Byron: 62-10
Templeton, John Samuelson: 64-5
Teniers, David: 55-19
Ter-Arutunian, Rouben: 59-19
Teraishi, Shosaku: 65-12
Teraski, George: 60-41
Terbrugghen, Hendrick: 62-20, ME-32
Terechkovitch, Kostia: 56-21
Terrell, Maurice: 57-16, 59-56
Terry, Alice: ME-75
Teshigahara: 60-2
Tesi, Mauro Antonio: 58-9, 61-22
Testa, Angelo: 53-17
Testa, Clorindo: 60-17
Testa, Pietro: 64-6
Teuber, Hermann: NE-96
Teunissen, T.: 61-20
Tevan,Rozsi: 62-40, ME-56
Teyral, John: 55-19
Tharrats, Juan Jose: 58-15, 64-17
Thayer, Abbott Handerson: 62-7, 62-17
Theisen, Earl: 57-16
Thelander, Henry: 52-5
Thelot, Jacob Gottlieb: 62-18
Theodor, Johann: 55-10
Thevenaz, Charles F.: 53-21
Thiebaud, Wayne: 60-3, NY-17, NY-18
Thiel, Midori Kono: 58-3
Thieler, Fred: 59-36, 64-14
Thiemann, Hans: NE-48
Thieme, Anthony: 57-30
Thiry, Paul: 58-1, 65-3
Thomas Edward: 61-35
Thomas, Elizabeth: 64-30
Thomas, Florence: 55-22
Thomas, Howard: 53-5, 61-35
Thomas, John Z.: 65-11
Thomas, Mary Leath: 53-5
Thomas, Neal: 56-2
Thomason, Tom W.: 62-10
Thompson, Bob: 60-43, 63-24
Thompson, Cephas: 58-14
Thompson, Helen May: 58-32
Thompson, William: ME-75
Thomson, Betty: 65-6
Thon, William: 53-1, 57-9, 64-31, ME-26, ME-73, ME-74
Thoren, Esaias: 54-18
Thorlaksson, Thorarinn B.: 66-2
Thormodsen, Norma: 53-26
Thornhill, James (Sir): 59-40, 61-22
Thorpe, Azalea: 53-24, 62-15
Thrall, Arthur: 55-2, 55-20, 56-25, 58-3, 60-3, 64-7, NY-3
Thrift, Walter: 61-35
Thurber, James: 59-6, ME-28
Thurm, Arnold: 53-1
Thurston, Gerald: 53-17
Thurston, Marcia Ann: 60-5
Tiebout, Cornelius: ME-29
Tiegreen, Alan: 65-11
Tiemer-Wille, Gertrude: 62-45
Tiepolo, Giovanni Battista: 57-18, 59-40, 62-20, 64-6, 67-19, NY-7&7b, NY-9
Tiepolo ,Giovanni Domenico: 55-24, 57-37, 64-6, 67-19
Tiepolo, Lorenzo: 55-24, 64-6
Tiffany, Louis Comfort: 62-7, 64-3
Tiffany, Virginia: 65-6
Tiffany & Company: NY-13
Tillett, Leslie & Doris: 57-6
Tilley, Lou: 58-16
Tillim, Sidney: NY-17
Ting, Walasse: 56-15, 58-15
Tintoretto, Jacopo Robusti: 55-24, 56-16, 57-18, 62-20
Tirrell, G.: ME-11
Tischler, Maynard G.: 62-10
Tissandier, Albert Charles: 64-5
Titian, Tiziano Vecellio: 57-18, 63-9, 67-19
Tittle, Juanita: 53-26
Tjepkema, J.M.: 61-20
Tlingit: 59-4
Tobase, Hodo: 58-42
Tobey, Mark: 52-11, 53-5, 55-9, 57-15, 58-42, 58-43, 59-7, 59-31, 60-4, 60-27, 62-27, 62-28, 64-2, 64-19, 65-11, ME-7, ME-41, ME-55, ME-65, NY-5, NY-20
Tock Jean: 58-16
Todd, Harold C.: 55-20
Todo: 64-17
Toeput, Lodewyk: 59-40
Tofel, Jennings: 56-2
Tofft, Peter Peterson: 64-1
Tollerz, Ulla: 57-14
Tolman, Stacy: 62-7
Tom Lee, Ltd: 61-30
Tomes, Marot: 52-7
Tomkins, Margaret: 56-13, 58-5
Tomlin, Bradley Walker: 57-30, 58-42, 60-27, ME-32, ME-59
Toney, Anthony: 56-2, 56-13, ME-73
Toney, Chester: 57-23
Tonomura: 63-21
Tony, Anthony: 61-15
Tooker, George: 58-40, 62-1, 63-7, 64-4, ME-73, NY-17
Toong, Shan-Ching: 56-27
Toque, Louis: 62-36
Torelli: 63-19
Toribio, Antonio: 63-29
Torkanowsky, Vera: 53-16
Torres-Aguero, Leopoldo: 60-17
Torres-Garcia, Joaquin: 59-23, 62-27, ME-55
Torro & Ferrer: 59-27
Torro, Ferrer, Knappen, Tippets, Abbett & McCarthy: 59-27
Torro, Ferrer, Torregrosa, Warner & Leeds: 59-27
Toselli, Angelo: 58-9, 59-40
Tostrrup J.: 57-40
Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de: 57-17, 57-18, 59-5, 62-5, 62-45, MMA-54-2, NY-21
Tourte, X. Suzanne: NE-96
Tourtelot, Madeline: 52-7, 56-2
Tovim, Y.: 58-36
Tovish, Harold: 63-31, 64-20, 58-6, 59-3
Town, Harold Barling: 60-15
Townley, Hugh: NY-10
Townsend, Neal: 62-10
Toy, Leland: 62-10
Toyokuni, Utagawa: 58-17, NY-12
Tozu, Keinosuke: 65-12
Tracy, Stanley: 56-27
Tragardh, Gota: 62-15
Traherne, Margaret: 58-35
Trajan, Turku: 61-2
Trange, J.M.: 51-3
Trapani, Mimi: 62-10
Traut Wolf: 55-10
Traver, Mary Dale: 62-10
Travis, Stuart: 59-6
Traynor, Ed: 53-24, 58-32
Treat, Rose: 60-5
Treccani, Ernesto: 58-40
Trefonides, Steven: 55-6, 59-56
Treiman, Joyce: 51-21, 55-5, 55-6, 56-13, 56-19, 58-16, 59-1
Treinin, A.: 58-36
Tremblay, Gerald: 59-3
Trenholm, Portia: 59-18
Treskow, Elisabeth: 61-1
Treumann, Otto: 61-20
Trevisani, Francesco: 62-36
Trieman, Joyce: ME-73
Trier, Hans: 59-36, 60-15, 61-4, 64-14
Trippetti, Joseph: 57-6
Trivigno, Pat: 51-21, 61-26
Trock, Paula: 62-15
Troekes, Heinz: NE-48
Troger, Paul: 59-40, 62-20
Trokes, Heinz: 59-36, 61-4
Trotter, McKie: 55-6, 57-23
Trotter, Newbold H.: 58-27
Troyon, Constant: 63-20, MMA-54-4
Trumbull: 54-25
Trumbull, John: 60-13, 62-17, ME-31
Tryggvadottir, Nina: 66-2
Tschumi, Otto: 60-15
Tsimshian: 59-4
Tsuji, Shindo: 63-23
Tsutakawa, George: 65-3
Tucker, Allen: NY-16
Tuerlinkx, Jean-Pierre: 61-1
Turcato, Giulio: 58-23, 60-15
Turchi M.: 58-9
Turnbull, William: 63-12
Turner: 55-19
Turner, Don La Viere: 65-11
Turner, J.M.W.: 63-20
Turner, Janet: 53-5, 58-3
Turner, Joseph Mallord William: 56-16, 62-20, 62-12, 63-17, 63-20, 65-10, 67-19, NY-9
Turner, Leslie: 57-3
Turner, Robert: 57-6, 60-5
Turner, Theodore: 55-20
Turoff, Muriel P.: 61-17
Tveteraas, Vilhelm: 57-40
Twachtman, John Henry: 62-7, 62-17, 63-1, NY-16
Twardowicz, Ruth Ann: 55-20
Twardowicz, Stanley: 58-12
Twatchman, J.H.: 64-3
Twery, Elliot: 53-5, 56-12
Twiggs, Russell: 55-6, 57-10
Twitty, James: 65-4
Twombly, Cy: 64-26
Tworkov, Jack: 61-29, 62-38, 64-29, 64-30, ME-73
Tyler, Kenneth W. (Rev.): 59-56
Tyrnauer, Francesca: 58-32
Tytell, Louis: ME-73
Tzonis, Aleco: 56-29
U.S. Coast & Geodetic Survey: 64-28
Ubac, Raoul: 62-8
Ucello, Paolo di Dono: 56-16
Uchima, Ansei: 60-3
Udvardy, John: 58-39
Ueda, Sokyu: 61-4
Ueeda, Hisahi: 65-12
Ugai, Hideo: 65-12
Ugarte, Juan Manuel: 60-17
Uhlmann, Hans: 56-7, 59-36, NE-48
Uk-chin, Chang: 58-42
Ulman, William A.: 58-3
Umlauf, Charles: 52-4, 58-16
Underhill, Irving: 64-28
Underhill, William: 62-10
Unesco World Art Series: 57-19
Ung-no, Yi: 58-33
Ungaro, Alberto: 60-2
Ungemann, Arne: 52-5
Unger, Carl: 54-18
Urban, Albert: ME-7
Uri, Aviva: 61-4
Urquhart, Tony: 58-6
Ushio, Takao: 65-12
Usui, Kichi: 58-42
Utamaro, Kitagawa: 58-17, NY-12
Utamaro, Utagawa: 60-38
Utley, Windson: 55-6
Utrillo, Maurice: 60-14
Utter, Bror: 57-23
Vaccaro, Michael A.: 62-45
Vacchi, Sergio: 60-20
Vachon, John: 57-16, 59-56
Vaga, Perino del: 62-20
Vaglieri, Giustino: 60-20
Vaiksnoras, Anthony J.: 55-2
Valadier, Giovanni: NY-21
Valadier, Giuseppe: 53-36, 58-9, 59-40
Valasquez: 57-18
Valberg, Britt-Marie: 57-14, 58-25, 60-12
Valentin, Silvia: 61-1
Valentini, Giovan Battista: 61-1
Valenza, Daniel Loomis: 57-14, 58-32, 62-10
Valeriani: 63-19
Valeska, Adolfas: ME-75
Valkema, Sybren: 61-1
Vallaton, Felix: 54-16, 62-5
Valtat, Louis: 60-14
Van Aken, Jan: 63-17
Van Beest, Albert: 64-1
Van Bentrum, Rik: 65-7
Van Bergen, Marten: NY-15
Van Bos, Cornelis: 63-9
Van Bouckhorst, Jan Philip: 55-24
Van Brunt, James R.: 64-1
Van de Velde, Jan: 55-24, 60-40, NY-9
Van Der Neer: 54-11
Van Der Rohe, Miles: 59-15, 62-34
Van Der Sluis, George: 57-10
Van der Straet, Jan: 59-40
Van Der Vaart, Jan: 61-1
Van Der Weyden, Rogier: 57-18, 64-9
Van Dongen, Kees: 63-14
Van Duzer, Clarence: 51-5
Van Dyck, Anthony: 57-18, 57-37
Van Dyk, James: 56-25
Van Everdingen, Allart: 55-24, 60-40
Van Eyck, Jan: 56-16, 57-18
Van Fraser, David: 53-17
Van Gelder, Lydia: 55-22
Van Gogh, Vincent: 57-18, 62-5, 63-14, ME-40, NY-7&7b
Van Gorp Ria Van Oerle: 61-1
Van Goyan: 54-11
Van Heusden, Wout: 51-3
Van Hoesen, Beth: 62-3
Van Honthorst, Gerard: 62-36, ME-32
Van Huysum, Jan: 63-14, NY-7&7b